<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<petfinder xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://api.petfinder.com/schemas/0.9/petfinder.xsd">
 <header>
  <version>0.1</version>
  <timestamp>2016-04-13T01:20:03Z</timestamp>
  <status>
   <code>100</code>
   <message/>
  </status>
 </header>
 <pet>
  <id>33216998</id>
  <shelterId>FL1067</shelterId>
  <shelterPetId/>
  <name>Max</name>
  <animal>Dog</animal>
  <breeds>
   <breed>Terrier</breed>
  </breeds>
  <mix>yes</mix>
  <age>Adult</age>
  <sex>M</sex>
  <size>L</size>
  <options>
   <option>hasShots</option>
   <option>altered</option>
   <option>housetrained</option>
  </options>
  <description><![CDATA[Max has been with us a year and is probably around 2 years old. We adopted him from Orange County Services  September of 2014 with the intention of fostering him. He was obviously never trained to walk on a lease or anything that most dogs would know by the time they are 9-12 months old.  He was house trained and he went right in a kennel from day one without a problem. We have had a trainer off and on for the past year help us with him. He has gotten better about walking on the leash, but we don't have the time to spend with him that he really needs. We have a bike tow leash and that is a good form of exercise for him when my husband can run him or a neighborhood boy can. He still jumps up sometimes. That has been a constant problem. He does great with the trainer but we haven't been as consistent with his training as would have been best. He is very energetic! Most of the time he is a sweet boy but if he has not had enough exercise he gets full of himself. He seems to like men, I think he must have had a male owner before. He loves my husband even though I do most of the work with him and feed him most of the time. He is a very loyal and affectionate dog. He hasn't been around children much and is unsure of things that he hasn't been around. When we first got him he was afraid of black trash bags out on the street, I don't think he had ever been in a car or out of the house he was first in.  He has become a very good watchdog. He is very alert  and interested in everything that is going on. If you are looking for a passive dog, Max is not it. If you are looking for a loyal, loving best friend Max could be for you. We have turned down people who don't have yards. I don't think an apartment is the right place for Max. We want to find him the best home we can for him. I have never fostered a dog before, and have gotten very attached to Max. He loves to ride in the car. It would be great if he could ride around with someone all day. Someone who lives out on a ranch or farm would be ideal or is home all day. My husband and I both work so we aren't home during the day much.

Contact: dustysutton@ymail.com]]></description>
  <lastUpdate>2016-01-04T08:17:15Z</lastUpdate>
  <status>A</status>
  <media>
   <photos>
    <photo id="1" size="pnt">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/1/?bust=1441610550&amp;width=60&amp;-pnt.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="1" size="fpm">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/1/?bust=1441610550&amp;width=95&amp;-fpm.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="1" size="x">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/1/?bust=1441610550&amp;width=500&amp;-x.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="1" size="pn">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/1/?bust=1441610550&amp;width=300&amp;-pn.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="1" size="t">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/1/?bust=1441610550&amp;width=50&amp;-t.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="2" size="pnt">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/2/?bust=1451895436&amp;width=60&amp;-pnt.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="2" size="fpm">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/2/?bust=1451895436&amp;width=95&amp;-fpm.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="2" size="x">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/2/?bust=1451895436&amp;width=500&amp;-x.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="2" size="pn">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/2/?bust=1451895436&amp;width=300&amp;-pn.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="2" size="t">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/2/?bust=1451895436&amp;width=50&amp;-t.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="3" size="pnt">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/3/?bust=1451895436&amp;width=60&amp;-pnt.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="3" size="fpm">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/3/?bust=1451895436&amp;width=95&amp;-fpm.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="3" size="x">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/3/?bust=1451895436&amp;width=500&amp;-x.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="3" size="pn">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/3/?bust=1451895436&amp;width=300&amp;-pn.jpg</photo>
    <photo id="3" size="t">http://photos.petfinder.com/photos/pets/33216998/3/?bust=1451895436&amp;width=50&amp;-t.jpg</photo>
   </photos>
  </media>
  <contact>
   <address1/>
   <address2/>
   <city>Winter Park</city>
   <state>FL</state>
   <zip>32792</zip>
   <phone>  </phone>
   <fax/>
   <email>contact@sniffingsnouts.com</email>
  </contact>
 </pet>
</petfinder>
